looks like they've got this place sealed
tight someone start a breach on the
front door we need to get out of here
before the whole base is on top of us
almost like someone woke them up
I suppose we could just wait here until
we're inevitably overwhelmed by our
attackers or I might suggest that
someone begin breaching the door point
taken Jessie get that door open
whatever you say commander there's that
famous McCree attitude I'll try to
adjust it for you boss wouldn't want to
cause any problems I thought we were
agreed commander snatch-and-grab that's
it
Antonia was right there was nothing we
could do to him now he's not our problem
anymore something tells me that won't be
the case
did you even consider what was going to
happen before you pulled the trigger I
made a decision I'll deal with the
consequences
oh I kiddin the four of us killed that's
not gonna happen
why'd you kill Antonio he make you angry
that all it takes
he thought he was untouchable he was
mistaken someone gets started on the
door do I have to do everything myself
didn't seem to be a problem earlier
anyone gonna start the bridge or should
we get Genji to cut a hole in the door
you heard the commander someone start
the breach
that door isn't going to breach itself
someone begin breaching the door
breaching device set now we wait
breach initiated now we wait starting
the breach might take a while if you
want something done right
patience is not my strong suit I suspect
we'll find something to occupy your time
so what do we do now boss we get out of
this room then head through the city to
the extraction point
after that we sit tight and hope someone
comes to pick us up quite a plan B
not sure why I was even worried I see
that everything is running as smoothly
as ever things go more smoothly when we
act like professionals
this mess was all worth it to see McCree
trying to pass himself off as a waiter I
thought I did just fine you got fired
from your cover job Jessie
lady was being rude she had a comin I
believe you found an expedient solution
commander here that the ninja agrees
with my decision you be sure to call him
as a character witness then
who was Antonia he's an arms dealer with
some other interests more and less
legitimate not anymore
Dantonio have any associates there's the
one who will probably take over for him
viale don't know too much about him then
doom fist and Ambani and a nominee who
runs a casino and monaco maximilian or
something
we're making progress on the door how's
everyone doing Oh couldn't be better
just grande here
how are you gonna explain this to the
strike commander you let me worry about
what Jack needs to know you know you
can't shoot him no but I could shoot you
I guess we're just assassins now no
matter what I do I cannot escape my fate
why are you so concerned about one death
McCree it's not the first time we've had
to kill this was an execution
dead is dead
a pity you missed the masquerade I have
the perfect costume didn't think that
would be your scene you're not the only
one who likes to dress up there's a lot
of things you don't know about me
still a ways to go on the door let's set
the clock a little shorter next time
twenty years and we still can't get a
door open we have to make these damn
things work faster
breaching process is still underway
we need more time to breach the door
breaching now get ready about damn time
everyone through the breach we're
getting out of here
urge you troublemakers might need a ride
to the art gallery
I'll pick you up there you heard her
let's move commander Reyes looks like
I'm gonna be your ride out of here
the commander's incapacitated but we'll
be there gallery cowboy
Talon seems very committed to ending our
lives better to kill them now than wait
for another surprise attack ironic
they seem determined to kill us I can't
imagine why we didn't have to go to all
this trouble if we were just gonna kill
Antonio it wasn't how I drew it up could
have fooled me
there was certainly a decisive solution
to the antoniou problem it's not how we
do things well it seems we've had a
change in methodology a little too much
change this is all your fault race I'm
never gonna hear the end of this am i
I'm sure I'll get over it eventually
good because I'm gonna need you Jessie
how are you feeling commander fine no
ill-effects so far let me know if that
changes I still think we should have
gone with the original plan of
disguising ourselves as the band do you
even play an instrument boss not well
details
feels like talent is mobilizing an
entire army to stop us
you just had to kick the hornet's nest
you seem awfully calm I take it all in
my stride
so much for keeping a low profile the
entire city must be awake now let's just
get out of here alive perhaps next time
we might select a less suicidal plan of
attack
you did would need it to be done Gabriel
don't apologize
I never have and I don't intend to start
now someone has to be the one to get
things done I feel no remorse for the
fate of these criminals at least
someone's on my side
Talon was tried to recruit my father he
didn't take them up on their offer he
didn't not find them to his liking their
aims did not coincide with his own
I wouldn't describe this as light
resistance quality intelligence we've
received it makes no difference to me
how droll even though we snuck that
surveillance system in to Antonio's
office our Intel's a little spotty
next time you should leave it to me I
can spy upon our enemies unseen and
undetected
and here I thought we were supposed to
be the quiet ones next thing you know
we'll have lieutenant Wilhelm on the
team we could use a tank it's not
exactly Carnevale she's serious I was
looking forward to the masquerade fair
enough
sure are a lot of them guess it's a good
thing we brought the ninja
good talk
what's it like Angie you know as a
cyborg pain and agony Hannah what am i
man who a machine then why did you agree
to it I wanted to be able to walk again
take better care McCree and hate for you
to need a body like mine
no offense Kinzie but I think I'm gonna
keep everything just the way it is a
couple more shots like that and they're
gonna have to make me a body like yours
Genji I wouldn't recommend it
we got ourselves a good old-fashioned
shootout on our hands
stealth has long since been an
impossibility
it's as though the whole city has been
mobilized against us she's how you like
what's the status commander Art
Gallery's insight we'll be there shortly
it should be smooth sailing from here oh
you had to say it didn't you I would
draw my previous comment we're
definitely not out of the woods yet I'll
note that for the record
that thing's bigger than Reinhart maybe
the worst has passed a worthy foe for my
blade
we should almost be out of the woods
watch out those things move faster than
they seem to oh come on what is that
thing
we made it to the art gallery but I
don't see you courtyard a little ways
past your position to curate and I'll
meet you there
except some company on the way in I'm
gonna try to shake them but it might
take a little while no problem we're
used to waiting around and getting shot
at and getting shot at you two are
adorable
fancy place here try to leave everything
in one piece tell that to them
you call this art a child could have
made it I never took you for an art
critic
enough art let's get out of here never
had the eye for it anyway Philistines
by the only one who feels hungry that
could be an unforeseen side effect I was
making a joke
looks like you're slowing down there
commander
shut up and keep shooting anyone else
hungry no what's your status pilot
where's the fun in that extraction
points in sight
antonio was right about one thing you
will take the blame for this always have
I don't need the statues and medals
anyway
greetings sir may I have your
reservation no reservation party of four
bit of a last-minute thing I'm terribly
sorry but we are unable to accommodate
walk-ins
name on your reservation here party of
four the names machree
as this is close to Carnevale as we're
likely to give you sound disappointed I
heard it was a good time
you know your brother would have made a
good agent
touchy subject
McCree we need to talk about your
Italian accent I watched a bunch of Old
Spaghetti Westerns I thought it was
pretty good
buona sera signora can I get you or
something to drink
please never do that again is this what
we become Gabriele
Blackwatch has always had one purpose to
do the real work of keeping the world
safe I thought you had the stomach for
it looks like I was wrong we're at the
extraction point where are you if you're
not coming soon you may as well turn
around whoa don't listen to him we're
getting out of here
you could all do with a little culture a
cowboy especially I'm plenty cultured
have you ever been to the cave of
mystery didn't think so
trust me Jesse you should know by now I
won't lead you wrong like you ever give
me a choice what's keeping our ride we
can't wait forever something tells me
the army of bad guys converging in our
position isn't helping macri's instincts
are as ever unimpeachable
no sign of rescue does nothing run on
time here this is your fault commander
we had a plan we could have walked
Antoniou right out of the city I didn't
sign up for this maintain operational
silence McCree everyone get ready to get
on board about damn time
I really anticipate the debriefing on
this debacle
this is it don't do anything stupid well
you clearly have that cover